totalhockey.com 2019-07-18

# Our Policies | Pure Hockey

Our website allows you to buy products and services, get information, enter contests, receive special discounts, apply for credit, fill out surveys, and receive newsletters, e-mails or other promotional information from us. We use the information that we collect about you to fulfill your product and service purchases and to create a more personalized online experience. This is just a brief overview, so please read on for more details about our Privacy Policy. This Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. Except as limited below, we reserve the right to use or disclose your personally identifiable information for business reasons in whatever manner desired.

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. For some services, we either collect and transfer personal information to a service provider you have selected, or you may visit other merchants through links on our site who may collect and use your personal information. In those cases the third-party service provider or merchant's privacy policy will govern how your information is handled. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others.

Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer  
Pure Hockey Corporate Offices  
89 Cross Street  
Holliston, MA, 01746

## What information does Pure Hockey collect from you?

In order to better provide you with numerous products and services, Pure Hockey collects two types of information about its visitors: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.

  1. Personally Identifiable Information

This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested when you register and set up an account, order a product or service, register for a Wish List, enter contests or sweepstakes, fill out surveys, and send us feedback. For example, this information might include your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other payment information, and product details. With this information, Pure Hockey can fill your orders and better provide you with personalized services. If you visit another site available through a link on our site, they will independently collect, use and share your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you have questions about their information practices, please read their privacy policies.

  2. Non-Personally Identifiable Information

This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you shop on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. For example, this information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop.

On an aggregated basis, we collect anonymous data related to the pages, products, downloads and other content that is sampled, clicked on, streamed, searched for, transferred from and downloaded. Except as otherwise limited in this Policy, we may disclose, sell, trade, or rent Non-Personally Identifiable Information to others without your consent.

## Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide Pure Hockey's visitors with a superior customized online experience. We use the customer contact information to fill orders, contact purchasers to inform them of their order status, to send promotional information, to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems.

Demographic data also may be collected at our site from third party advertising servers, content servers, or web site analysis agents who provide us with the zip code and area code associated with a visitor's server, along with pages viewed on our site. We review the actions of the Pure Hockey visitors on an aggregate basis to determine customers' preferences. Pure Hockey also does research on our visitors' demographics, interests, and pages viewed based on the information provided to us during ordering, a promotion, from our server log files, from our web site analysis agents, or from contests, drawings or surveys. We will use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site use, to improve our product offerings, and to customize our site's content, layout, and services. We receive reports from third party ad servers, content servers, or web site analysis agents that tells us how many ads were presented and clicked upon or what content was served or viewed.

We may also share your personally identifiable information with third parties who provide services to us, our customers and web site visitors. Those third parties include authorized contractors, temporary employees and consultants and other companies working with us (collectively, "agents"). Where we believe it to be appropriate (in our sole discretion), we will ask our agents not to disclose or use your personal information for purposes other than to provide services to you or Pure Hockey.

We gather information in the following ways:

  * Shopping

We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, to enable ads to be served on our site, to report Non-Personally Identifiable Information to our advertisers, and to monitor the level of activity on our site. We collect information from visitors to our site regarding the URLs they came from, domain types (e.g., .com or .org), their IP addresses, the date and time of their visit or order, the number of visits and orders, the number of visits per browsing session, the server type, the operating system and browser type used to come to the site, the country, state and telephone area code where their servers are located, the pages and page titles of our site that visitors viewed during their visit, whether the visitor's computer is enabled for Java or cookies, browser language, applications and plug-ins, and any search terms entered on our site.

  * Ordering

When you order from us, we collect personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or services, we will collect and maintain your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address, page you bought from and a password. We collect this, and other information, as disclosed in this Policy, in order to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials. Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contained and these changes will be automatically kept for future use. We may require additional verifications or information before accepting any order.

  * Gift Registry

If you decide to create a Wish List through our site, you will create an account, where we will collect and use your name, e-mail address, credit card or other payment information, billing and shipping address, phone number, password and product preferences. This information is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy except as explained here. Others will be able to search for your Wist List using your e-mail address unless you choose not to make your Wist List searchable. Those who have access to your Wist List will be able to see your name, e-mail address, city, state, and may have access to other personal information and product information that you have entered into the Gift List. If others place orders for items on your Gift List, they may have access to your address. We will use the product preferences that you include in your Gift List to inform you about offers that may be of interest to you. If you provide us with the e-mail addresses of your family and friends, we will use their e-mail addresses to send them your Gift List if you instruct us to. With your permission, we will send them the Gift List using your e-mail address as the originating address. We will not use the e-mail addresses of your family and friends for any other purpose.

  * Gift Cards

If you purchase a gift card from our site, you will give us the recipient's name and e-mail address if you wish to send the certificate by e-mail. If you wish to send a gift card by regular mail, you will give us the name, mailing information and phone number for the recipient. The recipient information you give us will only be used to send the gift certificate and for no other purpose.

  * Online Surveys and Polling

In order to improve our services to you, we ask some of our customers to voluntarily complete surveys, which may be collected by an independent third party. Individual survey answers are confidential, although Non-Personally Identifiable Information is collected and disclosed to third parties. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, simply decline to participate when asked.

  * Contests and Sweepstakes

When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask you for contact information such as your name, address and e-mail address in order to administer the contest, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners and make the winners' list publicly available pursuant to certain states' laws. Your consent to such promotional use and disclosure of this information is a condition of your participation. As a condition of receiving any prize, you will be required to submit an Affidavit of Eligibility, for us to ensure that you are eligible to receive the prize according to the Contest Rules.

  * Newsletters, Promotional E-mails

We offer free newsletters, promotional e-mails as a service to our customers. We will send you newsletters and e-mails periodically listing current specials and deals. You may "opt-out," or unsubscribe from our newsletters, emails or personalized on-line advertisements by following any unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail or newsletter you receive from us, or by sending an e-mail to "[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#224d52564d575662525750474a4d4149475b0c414d4f)". After doing so, if you have opted out of receiving all newsletters or promotional emails, you will not receive future promotional emails, newsletters unless you open a new account, enter a contest, or otherwise subsequently sign up to receive newsletters or emails. Please Note: If you agree to receive e-mails from any of our third party service providers or any third party merchants on our site, you will receive e-mails separately from them, and information that you choose to disclose to them will be subject to their privacy policy. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive their e-mails, you will need to follow their own specific opt-out instructions, as opting out to "[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0768777368727347777275626f68646c627e2964686a)" as described above will not opt you out of their promotional emails.

  * Contact Information and Third Party Data

If you contact Pure Hockey or our customer service representatives by telephone, e-mail or letter, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments. If you report a problem with our site, we may collect such information in a file specific to you. If you contact us through our feedback area or by calling one of our customer service representatives, we may ask for your name, e-mail address and order information in order to send you a reply.

  * Advertising

We may display advertisements on our site. By knowing a little about you, Pure Hockey will be able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content to you in the form of targeted banners and promotions. For example, advertisers give us an advertisement and tell us the type of audience they want to reach. Pure Hockey takes the advertisement and includes it in a Pure Hockey e-mail to prior customers meeting that criterion. We may also have third-party advertising servers display ads linked to certain search terms that you have entered, or to certain pages that you are viewing. In this process, advertisers never have access to individual account information. Pure Hockey may share aggregated data with advertisers. We may also use advertising partners to assist us in delivering personalized on-line ads to you through the use of cookies while you are on the Internet.

  * Web Site Use

We also track customers' traffic patterns throughout their online session, including which pages, information and advertisements a customer views while using the site and what items they place in their basket or purchase. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our site and to gather demographic information. We may share aggregated statistics about pages viewed on our site, sales and other shopping information with third parties.

  * Cookies

We use cookies and may allow others to use cookies in the operation of our site; to find out what cookies are and how they are used, click here.

  * Action Tags/Web Beacons

We may use and allow others to use action tags or web beacons in the operation of our site; to find out what action tags and web beacons are and how they are used, click here.

## Who is collecting your information?

  * Ad Servers and Content Servers

We may use third party ad servers or content servers to serve ads, product information, or other information both on and off our site. Those third parties may use "action tags" or web beacons throughout the site to count the number of visitors who click on a banner ad or other information and to track the number of customers who continue on to make a purchase. They may also place their own "cookie" on your computer to help those ads to run, analyze site usage and to provide you with personalized on-line advertisements. With respect to personalized on-line ad serving, our third party ad server may collect your first name and/or a product group/category (chosen by Pure Hockey based on your personal preferences and/or prior purchase history e.g., heads, gloves, helmets, etc.), which are used to serve you the most relevant personalized on-line ad. Except as set in the following sentence, we do not provide them with any of your Personally Identifiable Information. For more information about the information they collect, please see the section "Use of Cookies and Action Tags" below. To learn more about the information practices of the third party ad serving company used to serve ads on our site, Click here. To learn more about the information practices of the third party ad serving company used to serve you personalized ads, Click here.

  * Email Services

We use a third party (Constant Contact) to send promotional e-mails to customers. Images contained in the email may be served by the third party. They collect certain information about you such as your IP address, browser type, your operating system, the country and server your computer is logged onto, where the servers that your computer is logged onto is located, the time and date that a particular email was viewed, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular ad or email, products viewed and whether you continued on to make a purchase. They may use a "cookie" or "action tags."

  * Website Analysis Agent

We may contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and marketing. We use the services of marketing companies to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Action Tags and cookies provided by the marketing companies on this site. The type of information we collect includes things such as pages, information and advertisements viewed as well as what items are placed in a shopping basket or purchased, the order number, the amount of a purchase, the product number and the quantity purchased. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what kinds of customers our site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although the marketing companies log the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used.

  * Marketing Partners, Co-Branded Services, Framing/Windows on Third-Party Sites

We may run promotions for merchants where you may visit the merchants' sites. In some of those promotions, a window or frame containing the merchant's site may appear. Any time you are in a window, you should assume that your personal information is being collected, used and disclosed in accordance with that merchant's policies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you supply to those merchants. Any information that you share with them will be used and disclosed in accordance with that merchant's privacy policy. However, once you click on a return link to our site, you can expect that further information that you disclose will be treated in accordance with this Policy.

  * Links and Banner Ads to Third-Party Sites

Please be aware that our site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by this Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies or ad servers, which place advertising on our site may collect information about you through the use of cookies when you view or click on their advertising. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

## With whom do we share your information?

  * Other Parties Generally

We may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third parties, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information whatsoever. We may release account information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of Pure Hockey, our users, or others. If customers do not pay us for products ordered, we may submit their account information to a third party collection agency. We may also share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties who provide services to us, our customers and web site visitors. Those third parties include authorized contractors, temporary employees and consultants and other companies working with us. Where we believe it to be appropriate (in our sole discretion), we will ask our agents not to disclose or use your personal information for purposes other than to provide services to you or Pure Hockey.
